

# PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Sass
Javascript, React,C#
Photoshop,Figma
Bootstrap, TailwindCSS
PostgreSQL
NodeJs, ExpressJs,
Typescript, SharePoint,
Power Automate, Power Apps,
Power Apps Component
Framework

#### **PERSONAL SKILLS**

Creative spirit
Reliable and professional
Organized
Time management
Team player
Fast learner
Motivated

### LANGUAGE SKILLS

Engish - Advanced C1 German - Beginner A1

# CONTACT

P: +420 703 537 215 E: ladislav.topolsky@gmail.com A: 30 Years

# LADISLAV TOPOĽSKÝ

#### **ABOUT**

I am currently working as a Solution Lead in Adecco. Where I am developing and maintaining applications using MS Power Apps. In this role, I have learned a lot about communication with customers and providing them with a good roadmap to a successful finish for a project and support for ongoing projects. In my previous work experience as a software engineer, I learned a lot about software design and architecture. I have gained a better understanding between frontend and backend connection. I have a basic understanding of UX/UI design. In my role as HTML/CSS developer, I have worked with the headless CMS framework JellyPot where I have learned to build responsive webpages.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

IT SOLUTION LEAD / POWER APPS DEVELOPER

Adecco EMEA IT - Prague, CZ| February 2023 - Still

- Responsible for developing PowerApps model and canvas driven apps
- Extensive experience in the Microsoft Power Platform MS PowerApps, MS Power Automate (Flow)
- Experience with API or services integrations and a firm understanding of implementing solutions with multiple data sources.
- Designing solutions based on established patterns and best practices for SharePoint integration with other Microsoft products
- Designing and developing solutions for SharePoint that take advantage of standard web technologies, such as CSOM, REST, JavaScript, and OData
- Designing, developing, and customizing team sites, libraries, lists, views, and workflows

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Swift Shift - New York, USA| December 2021 - February 2023

- Responsible for developing microservice for fax integration with thirdparty API provider using NodeJS and ExpressJS.
- Designing the frontend solution of a full-stack application for job searching.
- Maintaining and developing part of the backend part of the application that was connected to multiple APIs.
- Responsible for developing and creating react components in Power Apps Component Framework.
- Designing and developing a frontend application with React with Microsoft authentification and GraphAPI service to connect to Sharepoint data source.
- Working daily to maintain the existing suite of Power Apps and continuously develop new features.

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Blue Lemons - Košice, Slovakia | June 2021 - December 2021

- Collaborating with back-end developers and web designers to build performant UI
- Ensuring the technical feasibility of UI/UX designs
- Designing UI elements, like menus, tabs and widgets
- Identifying and troubleshooting UX problems
- Conducting layout adjustments based on user feedback
- Adhering to style standards on fonts, colors and images
- Building page navigation buttons and search fields

#### HTML / CSS DEVELOPER

Anfas | January 2021 - June 2021

- Meeting with Web designers to discuss project design and layout.
- Coding the entire HTML site from end to end.
- Ensuring cross-platform compatibility.
- Troubleshooting application errors.
- Conducting website performance and usability tests.
- Meeting publication deadlines.

## **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

- HTML, CSS, SASS, JAVASCRIPT, TYPESCRIPT, SQL
- REACT, BOOTSTRAP, TAILWINDCSS, NODE, EXPRESS, PRISMA
- SHAREPOINT, POWER AUTOMATE, POWER APPS, POWER APPS COMPONENT FRAMEWORK
- PHOTOSHOP,FIGMA

#### **EDUCATION**

THE FACULTY OF ECONOMICS AND MANAGEMENT BACHELOR IN SYSTEMS ENGINEERING AND INFORMATICS

Czech University of Life Sciences Prague | 2019 - 2022

THE FACULTY OF ECONOMICS AND MANAGEMENT MASTERS IN SYSTEMS ENGINEERING AND INFORMATICS

Czech University of Life Sciences Prague | 2022 - 2024

#### CERTIFICATION

RESPONSIVE WEB DESIGN

FreeCodeCamp | June 2020

JAVASCRIPT ALGORITHMS AND DATA STRUCTURES

FreeCodeCamp | August 2020

FRONT END DEVELOPMENT LIBRARIES

FreeCodeCamp | July 2021